Raju Asani

Front End Developer with 6 years of Experience

To pursue a career in a reputed organization which helps me in enhancing my skills and where I can contribute to the best of my abilities and that provide me scope for growth which can help in achieving the goals of the company.



rasani8064@gmail.com

9113218064

Hyderabad, India

linkedin.com/in/asaniraju

github.com/rasani8064

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Software EngineerConcentrix Catalyst (formerly Prokarma)

09/2021 - Present

Hvderabad-India

Responsibilities

- Involved designing in web pages using HTML 5, CSS3, JavaScript, TypeScript, SASS, React.js, Redux, Angular
 9.
- Developed Responsive and Dynamic UI.
- Implemented stable React components and created Mono Repo using React and Angular to be added to any future pages.

Technology Analyst Infosys

05/2018 - 09/2021

Hvderabad-India

Responsibilities

- Learn and understand user interactions.
- Build reusable code and libraries for future use.
- Translating designs and wireframes into high-quality code.
- Collect feedback from design and technical staff on Website development needs.
- Integrate application front end with application business layer Bug fixes and unit testing.

Software Developer L&T Technology Services

04/2017 - 03/2018

Bangalore-India

Achievements/Tasks

- Follow best practices and standards for cross-browser compatibility.
- Ensure design consistency with client's development standards and guidelines.
- handling the Walkthrough sessions and requirement review meetings with team members.

SKILLS

HTML 5 CSS 3 JavaScript TypeScript

React JS Redux SCSS Angular Node JS(B)

Jest with RTL GIT Bitbucket Rest API

PROJECTS

Connected Unisim (Process Digital Twin) (09/2021 - Present)

A Process Digital Twin (PDT) is a live, virtual process representation
of a Plant. A digital twin is a digital representation of a real-world
entity or system. In the context of IoT, Digital Twins are linked to
real world objects and offer-information on the state of the
counterparts, respond to changes, improve operations and add
value

AML Social Web UI (Apple Customer Systems) (08/2020 - 09/2021)

 Social web is an application which is maintained to get all the complaints and requests raised on Social platform (Twitter). It is to get the customer complaints based on Posts and tags which are mentioned in twitter. Those posts which are assigned in twitter will assign a radar to the Team who responds on that post according to complaint or request raised in Social platform.

Zilker -SSE Online-WS (Apple Customer Systems) (09/2019 - 08/2020)

 Zilker is an On-boarding application and compliance validation tool built for ADE applicants. It acts as one stop tool to manage Questionnaires, application on-boarding, Workflow rules management, User submissions & review etc. Users can create their own Question/Questionnaire to join into the community.

Apple Admin Portal -YODA (12/2018 - 09/2019)

 Get support admin tool is used to manage configuration for major applications in Self Service Platform. Some admin tools are managed by Client and rest are managed by some portfolios. Intuitive Admins application is critical to Client Business Users, who depend on Admin applications to drive changes efficiently and on time.

EDUCATION

B.Tech SHAAZ CET (JNTU-HYD)

07/2009 - 06/2013

Hyderabad-India

Courses

CSE

LANGUAGES

English
Professional Working Proficiency

Telugu

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Hindi

Limited Working Proficiency